I appreciate some of y'all I like you
especially he clap oh wow yeah man I get
you I get you to appreciate like the way
you dress - that's a nice shirt on them
I'm trying to wear clothes that fit me
now you know I'm tired of holding my
stomach in I'm sorry
lose a little weight you know she's not
feeling proud when you lose your weight
start strutting in front of the mirror
don't series I'll be doing my poses and
everything I'm gonna have this flat
stomach by Christmas I am I want to rip
my shirt off like they used to do in the
old kung fu movies why would I do that
they get real serious you'll watch one
of them old conflicts sometimes they get
romantic with the lady man hey Shirl
come here
[Applause]
are you talking to me
i watch those movies every week a man I
used to think I can fight as I watch the
movies twice I would I watch come to
theatres Chinese connection into the
Dragon I was Bruce Lee at school every
Monday morning I go to school starting
fights Hey
[Laughter]
so then now is your name Tomlin
[Applause]
well then you say wanna fight you killed
my teacher and now I'm going to kill you
[Applause]
sometimes I walk around all day doing
stuff like that I was standing at the
gate hey what time is the fight sir you
need to step to the side they call the
police on me
my whole family crazy one of my sisters
thought a boyfriend was cheating on her
not too long ago she put crazy glue his
contact lens case you care so much you
seem shocked no the craziest thing about
that they are still together this is not
a joke he moved from st. Louis to Kansas
City because he got a better paying job
now he's instagramming her pitches with
his I messed up
he posing in the pictures like he's
still normal I can't make this up he'll
Instagram jizz
[Laughter]
he doesn't like me
my sister told me not to make jokes
about him I was like you gotta be
kidding me every time he comes to the
house I'll stand right next to him I
ain't man you want to go hang out come
on let's go to the club I'll keep my eye
on you subscribe to drive our comedy for
even more of the world's largest
collection of clean comedy